{
    "headerData": {
      "gender": "Other",
      "weight": 39,
      "completed": 21,
      "diagnoses": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "F10.221",
          "value": "Alcohol dependence with intoxication delirium"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "F10.251",
          "value": "Alcohol dependence with alcohol-induced psychotic disorder with hallucinations"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "M62.838",
          "value": "Muscle spasm, other, unspecified"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "F10.118",
          "value": "Alcohol abuse with intoxication delirium"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "ffgh",
          "value": "painscript active and in active"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "F10.121",
          "value": "Alcohol abuse with intoxication delirium"
        }
      ],
      "cycle": 21,
      "percent": "16%",
      "cycleHistory": [
        {
          "cycle": 16,
          "color": "Red"
        },
        {
          "cycle": 17,
          "color": "Green"
        },
        {
          "cycle": 18,
          "color": "Red"
        },
        {
          "cycle": 19,
          "color": "Red"
        },
        {
          "cycle": 20,
          "color": "Red"
        }
      ],
      "cycleStartDate": "05/27/2022",
      "comorbidities": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "F17.21",
          "value": "Nicotine dependence, cigarettes"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "G543.23",
          "value": "weed is harmful"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "f100.56",
          "value": "hand pain with swlling"
        },
        {
          "id": 0,
          "name": "ffc.098",
          "value": "c active and inactive"
        }
      ],
      "totalDays": 7,
      "phone": "2863433312",
      "dob": "05/01/1928",
      "name": "Rehaan Agrawal",
      "day": 6,
      "age": 94,
      "enrolled": "11/17/2021",
      "height": 155
    },
"summaryData": {
      "patientId": 31,
      "messageCount": 0,
      "responseCount": 0,
      "questions": [
          {
              "questionText": "Did pain affect your sleep last night?",
              "questionLabel": "Pain Affect Sleep",
              "questionId": 9,
              "dashboardType": "Icons",
              "bound": "Yes",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 19",
                      "submittedDate": "05/19/22, 10:52",
                      "date": "2022-05-19T05:22:52.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 16",
                      "submittedDate": "05/16/22, 01:22",
                      "date": "2022-05-16T07:52:05.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "Unsure",
                      "responseDate": "May 09",
                      "submittedDate": "05/09/22, 07:42",
                      "date": "2022-05-09T02:12:09.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Did you take any over the counter medications for your pain yesterday?",
              "questionLabel": "OTC Meds",
              "questionId": 16,
              "dashboardType": "Icons",
              "bound": "Yes",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 16",
                      "submittedDate": "05/16/22, 01:22",
                      "date": "2022-05-16T07:52:05.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 09",
                      "submittedDate": "05/09/22, 07:42",
                      "date": "2022-05-09T02:12:09.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Do you have any messages you would like to share with your Clinician today?",
              "questionLabel": "Message for Clinician",
              "questionId": 48,
              "dashboardType": "Text",
              "bound": "null",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "Nothing",
                      "responseDate": "May 11",
                      "submittedDate": "05/11/22, 03:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-11T10:03:06.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "Due to pain I am unable to sleep",
                      "responseDate": "May 09",
                      "submittedDate": "05/09/22, 07:42",
                      "date": "2022-05-09T02:12:09.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Has pain prevented you from going to work or completing normal activities today without difficulty?",
              "questionLabel": "Normal Activities",
              "questionId": 4,
              "dashboardType": "Icons",
              "bound": "Yes",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 11",
                      "submittedDate": "05/11/22, 03:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-11T10:03:06.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 06",
                      "submittedDate": "05/06/22, 12:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-06T07:03:28.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "On a scale of 0-10, to what extent are you feeling mentally defeated?",
              "questionLabel": "Mentally Defeated",
              "questionId": 45,
              "dashboardType": "Trend",
              "bound": "5",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "3",
                      "responseDate": "May 16",
                      "submittedDate": "05/16/22, 01:22",
                      "date": "2022-05-16T07:52:05.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "5",
                      "responseDate": "May 09",
                      "submittedDate": "05/09/22, 07:42",
                      "date": "2022-05-09T02:12:09.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Are you following the non-medicine options to treat your pain?",
              "questionLabel": "Physicial Therapy",
              "questionId": 33,
              "dashboardType": "",
              "bound": "None",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "Physical therapy",
                      "responseDate": "May 11",
                      "submittedDate": "05/11/22, 03:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-11T10:03:06.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "My current medications cause adverse effects",
              "questionLabel": "Adverse Effects",
              "questionId": 37,
              "dashboardType": "Icons",
              "bound": "Yes",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "No",
                      "responseDate": "May 11",
                      "submittedDate": "05/11/22, 03:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-11T10:03:06.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "On average, my treatment helps reduce my baseline pain by:",
              "questionLabel": "Pain Reduction",
              "questionId": 7,
              "dashboardType": "",
              "bound": "25% ,Not effective at all",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "50%",
                      "responseDate": "May 06",
                      "submittedDate": "05/06/22, 12:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-06T07:03:28.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "On a scale of 0-10, to what extent are you feeling depressed?",
              "questionLabel": "Feeling Depressed",
              "questionId": 46,
              "dashboardType": "Trend",
              "bound": "5",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "3",
                      "responseDate": "May 06",
                      "submittedDate": "05/06/22, 12:33",
                      "date": "2022-05-06T07:03:28.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Rate your level of fatigue during the day, if any, from 0 to 10.",
              "questionLabel": "Fatigue Scale",
              "questionId": 14,
              "dashboardType": "Trend",
              "bound": "5",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "3",
                      "responseDate": "May 19",
                      "submittedDate": "05/19/22, 10:52",
                      "date": "2022-05-19T05:22:52.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "On a scale of 0-10, to what extent are you feeling anxiety?",
              "questionLabel": "Feeling Anxiety",
              "questionId": 47,
              "dashboardType": "Trend",
              "bound": "5",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "2",
                      "responseDate": "May 19",
                      "submittedDate": "05/19/22, 10:52",
                      "date": "2022-05-19T05:22:52.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          },
          {
              "questionText": "Beck’s Depression Inventory",
              "questionLabel": "Beck’s Depression Inventory",
              "questionId": 8,
              "dashboardType": "Trend",
              "bound": "20",
              "history": [
                  {
                      "response": "14",
                      "responseDate": "May 20",
                      "submittedDate": "05/20/22, 12:42",
                      "date": "2022-05-20T07:12:54.000+00:00"
                  },
                  {
                      "response": "8",
                      "responseDate": "May 06",
                      "submittedDate": "05/06/22, 06:28",
                      "date": "2022-05-06T12:58:22.000+00:00"
                  }
              ]
          }
      ]
  }
}